<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><eng>	<translation id="x8_menu_onas" >		About us	</translation>	<translation id="x8_menu_omobile" >		Anout phone	</translation>	<translation id="x8_menu_galeria" >		Gallery	</translation>	<translation id="x8_menu_videa" >		Videos	</translation>	<translation id="x8_menu_zvuk" >		Sounds	</translation>	<translation id="x8_menu_porovnanie" >		Comparison	</translation>	<translation id="uvod_nadpis" >		Welcome to our website!	</translation>	<translation id="uvod_text" >		Welcome to the presentation and comparison of the two mobile phones. The project was based on the desired task from the course Fundamentals of media content. The site contains information on our cell phones, their comparison gallery of images, videos and sounds. Phone holders are the owners of this web-site Matej Belluš and Dominik Mikláš. And who exactly are we?	</translation>	<translation id="matej_bellus" >		Matej Bellus owner of the mobile phone Sony Ericsson W200i. Hey! My name is Matthew and I have 19 years studying the STU FIIT. High school I graduated from high school in Bratislava Hronca Jura. I completed the whole study in English. I live in Ružinov where I also grew up. I love water sports associated with it. In my spare time I am an inveterate alcoholic. I like to detox weekends where you find many new friends with whom I drink during the week then.	</translation>	<translation id="dominik_miklas" >		Dominik Mikláš owner of the mobile phone Sony Ericsson X8: Hi, my name is Dominik and I am 20 years I am a student of the Slovak Technical University, Faculty of Computer Science and Information Technology Department of Computer and Communication Systems and Networks. I come from a small village great Bierovce distant 10 km from Trencin. Completed secondary school education graduation I went to school Piaristická Joseph Braneckého in Trencin. My hobbies are put out to pasture sheep, poultry feeding and chasing after girls condensing meadow.	</translation>	<translation id="x8_menu_omobilesdf" >			</translation>	<translation id="x8_menu_omosdfbile" >			</translation></eng>